ROSICH MARCOS

UNITY 3D ARTIST

SUMMARY

I am a 3D artist located in Argentina and focused in the production of game assets to be used in Unity3D.

I work with Blender and am used to creating unitypackages with preconfigured models, materials and animation avatars, so that they can be easily added to any Unity project.

Since 2019 i have been participating in group and personal projects that helped me develop a full workflow and prepare myself to get introduced into a professional work environment.

I am currently looking for a remote position as an artist in the game developing industry and willing to learn any additional software needed, as well as relocating to another place.

WORK EXPERIENCE

3D CHARACTER ARTIST AND ANIMATOR

Nightmare Project June 2020 - Present

- Coordinated a small team of artists, and fixed the topology of their models
- Rigged characters according to the Unity conventions and animated them.
- Succeeded at modeling and texturing the main character, following a model sheet provided by a team member.
- Cooperated closely with programmers and designers to obtain the best final results.

GAME DEVELOPER

Personal Projects and Game Jams August 2020 - Present

- Learnt to use Git, exporting from Unity to WebGL and setting up an html page for the game.
- Got experience in Unity optimization techniques such as "Draw Call Batching"
- Got familiarized with working against the clock

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

SELF-TAUGHT

Skill Set Developing June 2020 - Present

UNIVERSIDAD TECNOLÓGICA NACIONAL - RESISTENCIA, ARG

Game Developing Course - Introduction to Blender, MakeHuman and programming games in C# using Unity3D January 2020 - May 2020

CONTACT INFO

- in linkedin.com/in/rosichmarcos
- mosichmarcos.com.ar
- rosichmarcos.artstation.com
- wa.me/5493404502729

SKILL SET

- Modelado Low Poly
- Pintado de Texturas Estilizadas
- Esculpido de Personajes
- Retopologización
- Rigging
- Animación
- Mapeo UV
- Materiales Procedurales
- Bakeado de Texturas y Normales
- Importación .FBX a Unity
- Configuración de animation controllers y rigs a Unity
- Generación de .unitypackages
- Control de versiones usando repositorios Git
- Programación C#

SOFT SKILLS

- Recibo y considero el feedback
- Deseo aprender y enseñar lo que sé
- Mantengo una comunicación permanente
- Me adapto a proyectos y equipos en constante cambio
- Valoro mucho la puntualidad

LANGUAGE

- Spanish: Native
- English (2011-2017): Limited Working Proficiency